22, and one of the invocation by the director, or campus ministries, Mr. Steve Whitewell.
I would always like to give just a little bit of a report.
We have about 150 athletes who attend our fellow subacristen athletes,
Bible studies each week and seven different teams.
Meetings at night have a chapel before the football games,
which we just completed, but I did all nine of those on the road in at home.
We do chapel before our basketball games, and we'll be hosting a Thanksgiving dinner
for our international students next week for our national athletes.
We have 42 international athletes at NEO from 18 different countries.
So, pray for us.
Father, we thank you for this night.
We thank you that we can come together as a community,
Mayor Parker, manager Reese, and all of our council people,
and all of our good city people that support us and take care of us every day.
Father, help them make good decisions.
Just bless our country, bless our election process tomorrow.
God bless America and Jesus name. Amen.
I want to say it's a miracle.
And two of the Republicans will let you stand.
One nation under the end of his will, with liberty and justice for all.
Poor public in front of schedule personal appearances.
Budget amendment.
Mr. Mike.
Adding.
Thank you, Mayor.
On the last council meeting we brought up a budget amendment to you for $65,000.
The purchase of property.
We did not take into account the closing cost.
The closing cost are $1,000, $29.
And $4 cents.
We're asking to approve this budget amendment to finish the closing on the property that we agreed to purchase.
When's that closing?
Come on.
Thank you, Mike.
6.
Good.
I'm seven and eight.
279 Davis writes remain claim for pencil told jrd a.
We're licensing and associated complaint proceedings and amount of to.
$157.
So Mayor and members of the Council in your packet, you should have a BA, which describes the details
of this particular invoice for Davis-Rectour Main.
These professional services and disbursements incurred from September 7th through September
30th.
Primarily, I would tell you that this had to do with the current legal proceedings and preparation
for the technical conference to review GRDA's updated study report.
All the above, we had emails, email exchanges, and we actually had several briefings via
teams that we got together and discussed not only strategy, but some of the reports,
and they, like, have our guidance on some particular items, not how they proceed during
the technical conference.
So you'd say the majority of it was international or, like, a teleconference or, yeah, it's probably
half an half, probably half phone calls an email and the other half is the meetings.
Just curious, I was always thought about that, like, do we have a rate for email, rate
for?
Nope.
We have an hourly rate.
It's a build an hourly rate no matter.
Yeah.
10.
2023 meeting schedule.
We have to have these done by a certain date for the period for the next year, so we discussed, maybe
trying to move some of these, but to move them all to Tuesdays, but with Brian's new
job, there's going to be difficult for him to make those, I think.
Right.
No, I don't think so.
The only issue is the fact that he...
Okay.
Did we move those to six?
It'll be okay.
It's okay.
So that's why they're still in my days with the occasional Tuesdays because of the holidays.
But that won't start to the first year, correct?
What you only got a couple left.
Yeah.
I don't have those unless we have to in November December, right?
Motion to approve.
Second.
I love them, any new business, which is written to the posting of this agenda, 12 staff reports, 13 trusty community announcements, 14 adjournment.